Finding Aid for the Poster Collection LSC.0095
UCLA Library Special Collections
- World War I--France (17), U.S. (36)., 53 items. (Box 18)
  - Sugar means ships / The consumption of sugar sweetened drinks must be reduced / For your beverages 400 million lbs. of sugar were imported in ships last year. Every ship is needed to carry soldiers and supplies now. [Washington, D.C.?]: United States Food Administration, [1917] (New York: The Ca
    Signed in lower left of image: "E. Fuhr." USFA emblem in top left. Printer's device at bottom left (wings with wheel reading: "the seal of quality"). DPP symbol (Committee on Public Information, Division of Pictorial Publicity) at left of image. Date from LC record.
  - The deadly question / "What am I doing to help win the war?" / Work Serve Save / And you? Washington, D.C.: National War Savings Committee Advertising Service Division, [191- ]., 1 print: 1 color (black); 63 x 41 cm. (Box 18)
  - The girlhood of America is her second line of defence / YWCA will tell you what America expects of her girls / A call to the colors. [S.l.]: Y.W.C.A., [191-]., 1 print: color; 75 x 51 cm. (Box 18)
    All text except for the "YWCA" in its upside down triangle logo. 4 areas of text: 3 horizontal in a vertical stack and 1 vertical down the left side.
  - The Queen of Belgium appealed to the Red Cross to aid in saving the children / The children are the hope and future of Belgium. [S.l.]: War Council of the American Red Cross, [191-]., 1 print: 2 color (black and red); 53 x 35 cm. (Box 18)
    Artist's signature at bottom left of image: "A.T.F." Under the text: "Bulletin No.8 -- issued by the War Council of the American Red Cross to show the people of America how their generous contributions are being expended in the interest of humanity." At bottom center: "Post in a conspicuous place -- A.S. Burleson, Post-Master General."
  - The Red Cross supplies 30,000 people each week with information concerning relatives in the fighting forces at home and overseas ... [S.l.]: War Council of the American Red Cross, [191-]., 1 print: 2 color (black and red); 53 x 36 cm. (Box 18)
    Text only with Red Cross emblem underneath. At lower right: "Bulletin No. 10 -- issued by the War Council of the American Red Cross to show the people of America how their generous contributions are being expended in the interest of humanity." At bottom center: "Post in a conspicuous place -- A.S. Burleson, Postmaster General"
  - They give their lives / Do you lend your savings? [Washington, D.C.?]: Committee on Public Information Division of Pictorial Publicity, [191-]., 1 print: color; 76 x 51 cm. (Box 18)
    Signed in bottom right: "H.D. Welsh." W.S.S. emblem in middle right of image.
  - Uncle Sam's job: Armenia and Syria. Denver, Colo.: United States National Bank, 1917 (Denver, Colo.: Smith-Brooks Co.)., 1 print: 2 color (red and blue); 82 x 56 cm. (Box 18)
    At bottom: "Albert A. Reed, Treas." Date from LC.
  - United we serve / Y.M.C.A., Y.W.C.A., National Catholic War Council - K. of C., Jewish Welfare Board, War Camp Community Service, American Library Association, Salvation Army / United War Work Campaign $170,500,000. [S.l.: s.n., 1918]., 1 print: color; 71 x 51 cm. (Box 18)
  - War rages in France / We must feed them / They cannot fight and raise food at the same time / Denying ourselves only a little means life to them. [Washington, D.C.?]: United States Food Administration, [191-]., 1 print: 2 color (gray and black); 76 x 51 cm. (Box 18)
    At lower left: "No.19." USFA emblem at bottom.
  - We belong 100% strong. [S.l.: Red Cross?], 1919., 1 print: 2 color (blue and red); 61 x 46 cm. (Box 18)
  - When you fire remember this / Enlist in the Navy. [S.l.: United States Navy?, 1917]., 1 print: color; 42 x 30 cm. (Box 18)
    Signed in lower right of image: "W.A. Rogers". Text covers the back: "A word to you..." (motivating men to enlist). Date from LC record.
  - Where the victims are / Save the survivors -- 3,950,000 starving people / Campaign for $30,000,000. New York: American Committee for Relief in the Near East, [1917?]., 1 print: color; 54 x 71 cm. (Box 18)
    At bottom: "1 Madison Ave. New York City; Cleveland H. Dodge, Treasurer." Area, population, and death statistics to left of map.
  - Workers lend your strength to the red triangle / help the "Y" help the fighters fight / United War Work Campaign -- November 11 to 18. [S.l.]: Y.M.C.A., [1918]., 1 print: color; 68 x 50 cm. (Box 18)
    Signed in lower right of image: "Gil [artist's mark] Spear."
  - Y.W.C.A. [S.l.]: Y.W.C.A., [191-]., 1 print: 1 color (blue); 56 x 41 cm. (Box 18)
    YWCA logo only.
  - YMCA ... United War Work Campaign November 11-18, 1918. [Washington, D.C.?]: Division of Pictorial Publicity, 1918 (New York: Alco-Gravure, Inc.), 1 print: 2 color (brown and red); 84 x 56 cm. (Box 18)
    Portrait artist's signature illegible (S.J. Wauk?). Text caption: "Cabled from France August 21st, 1918."
- World War I--France., 2 items.
- World War I--U.S., 6 items. (Box 20)
  - "The sword is drawn / The Navy upholds it!" New York: H.C. Miner Litho. Co., [1917]., 1 print: color; 106 x 71 cm. (Box 20)
    Signed in lower right of image with artist's monogram. Printed under bottom left of image: "Painted by Kenyon Cox, N.A." At bottom under title: "U.S. NAVY RECRUITING STATION 117 West Ocean Street Long Beach." Printer's logo in lower left of image, which includes number: "19686." Date from LC record.
  - For every fighter a woman worker / United War Work Campaign / Care for her through the YWCA. New York: American Lithographic Co., [1918], 1 print: color; 104 x 76 cm. (Box 20)
    Signed in lower left of woman: "ADOLPH TREIDLER." Model for woman reportedly became artist's wife. Date from known campaign.
  - Help deliver the goods / Do it now. New York: American Lithographic Co., [191-], 1 print: color: 103 x 61 cm. (Box 20)
    Signed in bottom right of image: "PAUS." Bottom of poster reads: "117 West Ocean St., Long Beach." Tag on shells reads: "to be delivered RUSH."
  - His home over there / More than 2000 such homes for our boys / United War Work Campaign, November 11th-18th. [S.l.]: Y.M.C.A., [191-] ([Washington, D.C.?]: Committee on Public Information Division of Pictorial Publicity)., 1 print: color; 105 x 71 cm. (Box 20)
    Signed in bottom right: "ALBERT HERTER." Red YMCA and blue YWCA emblems flanking the top text. At bottom left, under image: "4104." Publisher's emblem at lower right of image.
  - If you can't go across with a gun come across with your part of the Red Cross War Fund. [S.l.]: Red Cross, [1917] (New York: The United States Printing and Lithograph Co.)., 1 print: color; 103 x 70 cm. (Box 20)
    Signed in lower left of image where text begins: "C.W. LOVE." Printed on newsprint? Date from LC record.
  - Men wanted for the Army. [S.l.: United States Army?, 191-]., 1 print: color; 103 x 75 cm. (Box 20)
    Signed in lower right of image: "Michael P. Whelan." At bottom margin in decorative long horizontal vignette: "APPLY AT 1705 Lawrence Street Denver, Colorado RECRUITING STATION." Under lower left of vignette: "Form No. 404, A.G.O." Some paper losses in acid-free envelope under poster.
- World War I--U.S., 6 items. (Box 27)
- World War I--U.S., 6 items. (Box 26)
- World War I--U.S., 6 items. (Box 25)
- World War I--U.S., 6 items. (Box 24)
  - 20,000 tons of clothing desperately needed by Germany's victims in Belgium and Northern France / Germany will not clothe them America must ... Newark, NJ: Commission for Relief in Belgium, [191-] (New York, New York: Allied Printing Union Label), 1 print: 2 color (red and blue); 96 x 64 cm. (Box 24)
  - All together! Enlist in the Navy. [S.l.: s.n.], [19]17., 1 print: color; 78 x 109 cm. (Box 24)
    Signed in lower right: "H. Reuterdahl U.S.N.R. '17."
  - Four years in the fight / The women of France / We owe them the houses of cheer / United War Work Campaign. [S.l.]: Y.W.C.A., [1918] (Cincinatti; New York: Strobridge Litho. Co.), 1 print: color; 107 x 71 cm. (Box 24)
    Signed: "L. Jonas." Dimensions from LC record. Date from other posters for the same campaign.
  - This device on hat or helmet means U.S. Marines. [S.l.: s.n., 191-]., 1 print: color (mostly green and yellow); 107 x 71 cm. (Box 24)
    Signed in lower right of image: "F"(artist's monogram). Tears repaired with contemporaneous stamps that read: "Keep your W.S.S. Pledge."
  - Treat 'em rough! Join the tanks. [Washington, D.C.?]: United States Tank Corps., [1917] (Chicago; New York; St. Louis: National Printing & Engraving Co.)., 1 print: color; 104 x 72 cm. (Box 24)
    Signed in lower left: AUGUST HUTAF." At lower right: "010824." Large bottom margin blank.
  - U.S. Marines / Good pay, foreign travel, congenial employment. [S.l.: s.n., 191-]., 1 print: 2 color (black and yellow); 101 x 76 cm. (Box 24)
    Central photo caption: "Soldiers of the sea."
- World War I--U.S., 6 items. (Box 23)
  - Another notch Chateau Thierry / U.S. Marines. [S.l.: s.n., 191-]., 1 print: 2 color (brown and black); 101 x 77 cm. (Box 23)
    Signed at lower left of image: "Adolph Treidler."
  - Columbia calls / Enlist now for U.S. Army. [New York?: s.n.], c1916., 1 print: color; 101 x 76 cm. (Box 23)
    At bottom left: "DESIGNED BY FRANCES ADAMS HALSTED." At bottom right: "Painted by V. Aderente." Poem at lower right by Halsted. Text continues at bottom: Nearest Recruiting Station (printed) Army Recruiting Station 1705 Lawrence Street Denver, Colorado (stamped).
  - Follow the flag / Enlist in the Navy. New York: Carey Print Lith., [19]17., 1 print: color; 105 x 71 cm. (Box 23)
    Signed in lower right of image: "J. Daugherty 17 / Composition H.R. (Henry Reuterdahl?)." Text continues: U.S. Navy Recruiting Station Union Oil Bldg., Los Angeles.
  - That Liberty shall not perish from the earth / Buy Liberty Bonds / Fourth Liberty Loan. New York: Heywood Strasser & Voigt Litho. Co., [1918]., 1 print: 2 color (orange and brown); 104 x 72 cm. (Box 23)
    Signed in lower left: "IOSEPH PENNELL DEL." Date from other 4th Liberty Loan posters.
  - They kept the sea lanes open / Invest in the Liberty Loan. New York: W.F. Powers Litho, [1919?]., 1 print: color; 99 x 75 cm. (Box 23)
    Signed in lower right: "L.A. SHAFER."
  - We need you! Coast Artillery Corps U.S.A. New York, NY: Rode & Brand Litho., [191-]., 1 print: color; 64 x 97 cm. (Box 23)
    Signed in upper right: "TOLSON."
- World War I--U.S., 6 items. (Box 21)
- World War I--U.S., 6 items. (Box 31)
- World War I--U.S., 6 items. (Box 22)
  - And they thought we couldn't fight / Victory Liberty Loan. [S.l.: s.n., 1919]., 1 print: color; 105 x 78 cm. (Box 22)
    Signed in lower left: "CLYDE FORSYTHE." At bottom left: "5-C."
  - Come along / Learn something see something in the U.S. Navy / Ample shore leave for inland sights. New York: Press Navy Recruiting Bureau, [1919]., 1 print: color; 108 x 71 cm. (Box 22)
    Signed in bottom right of image: "JAMES H. DAUGHERTY." At bottom left under image: "Painted by James H. Daugherty." Image Caption: "SOUTH AMERICA." Date from LC.
  - Fight or buy bonds / Third Liberty Loan. Boston: Forbes, [19]17., 1 print: color; 101 x 76 cm. (Box 22)
    Signed in lower right: "Howard Chandler Christy 1917." At bottom left: "2A." Poster design made in 1917, although Third Liberty Loan was in Spring 1918. Poster may have been printed in 1918, or printed in 1917 after the end of the Second Liberty Loan (fall 1917) and not distributed until 1918.
  - Get under this fighting top / Navy and Naval Recruiting Station. [S.l.]: Recruiting Inspector Western Division U.S. Navy, [n.d.] (San Francisco: Galloway Litho.), 1 print: color; 108 x 71 cm. (Box 22)
    Printed at lower left: "RAYMOND BANNISTER."
  - I want you for the Navy. Boston: Forbes, 1917?, 1 print: color; 105 x 69 cm. (Box 22)
    Signed in lower right next to woman: "Howard Chandler Christy. 1917." At bottom: "Promotion for anyone enlisting. Apply any recruiting station or postmaster."
  - La Croix de Guerre des Femmes / "Let it rest on my shoulder now" -- American woman. New York: Alpha Litho. Co. Inc., [191-]., 1 print: color; 99 x 69 cm (Box 22)
    At lower left of image: "Compliments of D.W. Griffith whose artcraft picture, "The Great Love," reveals officially the war work of English women."
  - U.S. Marines / Serve where you see the red star / Enlist today. [Colorado?: s.n., n.d.]., 1 print: color; 80 x 107 cm. (Box 22)
    Under image: "At 1605 Larimer Street." [Denver, Colorado].
- World War I--U.S., 6 items. (Box 30)
- World War I--U.S., 6 items. (Box 32)
- World War I--U.S., 6 items. (Box 33)
  - A Wonderful opportunity for you / United States Navy offers to American citizens of good character ... the best chance to see the world, save money and serve their country [text blocks] [New York?: New-Art Lithographic Company Inc.?, 1917?] New York, N.Y.: New-Art Lithographic Company Inc., [1917], 1 print: color; 96 x 53 cm. (Box 33)
    Signed in lower right of image: "RUTTAN." Monogram just above: "RKC 2"(inside a triangle). Image caption: "GOING HOME-ON LEAVE." Publisher, printer, and date from LC record of slight variant.
  - Be a U.S. Marine / First in the fight~ Always faithful~ [S.l.: s.n., 191-], 1 print: color; 107 x 71 cm. (Box 33)
    Signed in lower right of image: "JAMES MONTGOMERY FLAGG." Text at bottom of poster: "Apply at 1605 Larimer Street, Denver, Colo." Bottom tears patched on front and back with stamps reading: "Keep your WSS pledge."
  - Enlist in the Navy / To Arms / U.S. Navy Recruiting Station 117 West Ocean St. Long Beach. [S.l.: s.n., 191-]., 1 print: color; 98 x 68 cm (trimmed). (Box 33)
    Signed in right under image: "MILTON BANCROFT."
  - Joan of Arc saved France / Women of America save your country / Buy War Savings Stamps. [Washington, D.C.?]: United States Treasury Department, [191-] (New York: The United States Printing & Lithograph Co), 1 print: color; 101 x 76 cm. (Box 33)
    Signed in lower left of image: "Haskell Coffin." Image of the War Savings Stamp at left of bottom text area. At bottom margin: "S-1"
  - Must children die and mothers plead in vain? / Buy more Liberty Bonds. New York: The Sackett & Wilhelms Corporation, [1918], 1 print: color; 101 x 76 cm. (Box 33)
    Artist's monogram in middle right of image. At bottom left margin: "1-B"
  - Oh, boy! That's the girl! / The Salvation Army Lassie keep her on the job / Nov. 11th-18th 1918 United War Work Campaign. New York: The Sackett & Wilhelms Corporation, 1918., 1 print: color; 101 x 75 cm. (Box 33)
    Signed in lower left of image: "G M RICHARDS."
  - Save your child from autocracy and poverty / Buy War Savings Stamps. [Washington, D.C.?]: United States Treasury Department, [191-] (New York: The United States Printing & Lithograph Co), 1 print: color; 103 x 76 cm. (Box 33)
    Signed in upper right of image: "HERBERT PAUS." Image of the War Savings Stamp at right of bottom text area. At bottom left: "S-1." Visible printing lines at top and bottom.
  - The Navy put 'em across / The Service for Travel and Training Ages 17 to 35 / Apply Navy Recruiting Station. [S.l.]: Press U.S. Navy Recruiting Bureau, 1918., 1 print: color; 117 x 74 cm. (Box 33)
    Signed in lower right of image: "H. Reuterdahl US.N '18." Stamps reading: "Keep your W.S.S. Pledge" used on verso to repair some of the tears.
- World War I--U.S., 104 items. (Box 36)
- World War I--U.S., 6 items. (Box 29)
- World War I--U.S., 6 items. (Box 28)
- World War I--U.S., 6 items (3 posters on poor mats). (Box 34)
  - Americans all! / Victory Liberty Loan. Boston: Forbes, 1919., 1 print: color; 101 x 68 cm. (Box 34)
    Signed in lower right of image: "Howard Chandler Christy." Honor Roll of 14 names along right side. At lower left: "4-C."
  - Join the Navy / the service for fighting men. [S.l.: s.n., 191-]., 1 print: color; 105 x 72 cm. (Box 34)
    Signed in lower right of image: "-Babcock-."
  - Keep 'em smiling! / help war camp community service / "morale is winning the war" / United War Work Campaign. [S.l.: s.n.], 1918., 1 print: color; 106 x 71 cm. (Box 34)
    Signed in lower left of image: "M. LEONE BRACKER." War Camp Community Service emblem in lower left text area.
  - On the job for victory / United States Shipping Board Emergency Fleet Corporation. Philadelphia, P.A.: Publications Section Emergency Fleet Corporation, [191-]. ([Washington, D.C.]: Department of Pictorial Publicity), 1 print: color; 76 x 98 cm. (Box 34)
    Signed in lower left of image: "JONAS LIE."
  - Sure! We'll finish the job / Victory Liberty Loan. Chicago: Edwards & Deutsch Litho. Co., 1918., 1 print: color; 95 x 66 cm. (Box 34)
    Signed in lower left of image: "Gerrit A. Beneker." At lower left: "I-C."
  - The greatest mother in the world / Red Cross Christmas Roll Call Dec. 16-23rd. [S.l.]: American National Red Cross, 1918 (Chicago: Edwards Deutsch Litho. Co.)., 1 print: color; 106 x 71 cm. (Box 34)
    Signed in lower right of image. Some tears repaired with Red Cross stamps reading: "Red Cross Christmas Roll Call 1918" and "100%."
  - The Navy needs you! Don't read American History -- make it! New York: The H.C. Miner Litho. Co., [191-]., 1 print: color; 107 x 71 cm. (Box 34)
    Signed in lower right of image: "JAMES MONTGOMERY FLAGG."
  - U.S. Navy / Help your country / Enlist in the Navy / Navy Recruiting Station / 117 West Ocean St., Long Beach. Brooklyn, N.Y.: Latham Litho & Ptg. Co., [191-]., 1 print: color; 104 x 71 cm. (Box 34)
    Signed in lower right of image: "H. Reuterdahl." At lower left under image: "Courtesy of R.J. Collier, Esq."
- World War I--U.S., 11 item (posters folded). (Box 37)
- World War I--U.S., 6 items (posters folded). (Box 38)
- World War I--U.S.(2), Britain (1)., 3 items (2 posters on poor mats). (Box 35)
  - For every fighter a woman worker / Y.W.C.A. / Back our second line of defense / United War Work Campaign. New York: The United States [Printing &] Lith Co., [191-]., 1 print: color; 105 x 69 cm. (Box 35)
    Signed in upper right of image: "ERNEST / HAMLIN / BAKER."
  - Over [T]here! / Skilled Workers / On the ground [behind the lines] in the Air Service ... [S.l.: United States Air Service?, 191-]., 1 print: color; 84 x 72 cm (trimmed). (Box 35)
    Signed in lower right of image: "LOUIS~ / FANCHER." In lower left of image: "PRO~ / PATRIA." Poster trim and in-painting seem to be attempt to make poster only applicable to homefront work.
- World War I--United States (3), Britain (1)., 4 items. (Box 14)
- World War II--France., 2 items. (Box 17)
- World War II--France., 6 items. (Box 16)
- World War II--France., 6 items. (Box 15)
- World War II--Germany., 2 items. (Box 11)
- World War II--Germany., 2 items. (Box 12)
- World War II--Germany., 2 items. (Box 13)
- World War II--U.S., 15 items. (Box 44)
- World War II--U.S., 16 items. (Box 48)
- World War II--U.S., 15 items. (Box 47)
- World War II--U.S., 15 items. (Box 45)
- World War II--U.S., 15 items. (Box 43)
- World War II--U.S., 15 items. (Box 42)
- World War II--U.S., 15 items. (Box 41)
- World War II--U.S., 15 items. (Box 46)
- World War II--U.S. (10), Canada (1)., 11 items. (Box 49)
- World War II--U.S. (47), Netherlands? (3), France (26)., 76 items. (Box 19)
  - "In the strength of great hope we must shoulder our common load" / Buy Victory Bonds. [Washington, D.C.]: U.S. Treasury Department, 1945 ([Washington, D.C.]: U.S. Government Printing Office)., 1 print: color; 66 x 47 cm. (Box 19)
    Signed in lower right of image: "c.c. beall." At lower right: Victory Loan emblem. At bottom: "1945--O-662911 / An Official US Treasury Poster / WFD 32." Issued as a memorial to FDR after his passing.
  - "No loyal citizen to the United States should be denied the democratic right to exercise the responsibilities of his citizenship, regardless of his ancestry ..." The President of the United States, February 3, 1943. Washington, D.C.: Office of War Information, 1943 (Washington, D.C.: U.S. Government Printing Office)., 1 print: 2 color (black and red); 51 x 21 cm. (Box 19)
    At lower left: "OWI Poster No.75." At lower right: "1943--O-533582."
  - "One swine too many..." / The Nazis in Holland tried to spread the idea that slaughtering unweaned calves would leave more milk for dutch children. They devised the slogan - "One calf too many means no milk for eight children." Dutchmen, however, altered the slogan to read - "One swine too many means starvation for many people." [Netherlands?: s.n., 1945?]., 1 print: color; 75 x 51 cm. (Box 19)
    Dutch poster printed for display in Allied English-speaking countries. (Publication information from Midden-Holland Regional Archives).
  - "This world cannot exist half slave and half free" / Fight for freedom! Washington, D.C.: Graphics Division Office of Facts and Figures, 1942 (Washington, D.C.: U.S. Government Printing Office), 1 print: 2 color (black and brown); 51 x 36 cm. (Box 19)
    Signed in lower left of image: "JOHN FALTER." At bottom: "1942-O."
  - Allies for a big job / OCD / Cooperate with your local Defense Council. [Washingont, D.C.?: Office of Civilian Defense?], 1942 ([Washington, D.C.]: U.S. Government Printing Office)., 1 print: color; 50 x 54 cm. (Box 19)
    Signed in lower right: "EMILY NEWMAN." At lower right: "1942--O-473121."
  - Attack attack attack / Buy War Bonds. [Washington, D.C.]: U.S. Government Printing Office, 1942., 1 print: color; 71 x 56 cm. (Box 19)
    Signed in lower left of image: "FERDINAND WARREN 42." At bottom: "1942-- O-497775 / WSS 697-C."
  - Can all you can / It's a real war job. Washington, D.C.: Office of War Information, 1943 (Washington, D.C.: U.S. Government Printing Office)., 1 print: color; 57 x 41 cm. (Box 19)
    At lower left: "OWI Poster No.77." At lower right: "1943--O-533993."
  - Conserve rubber for National Defense ... Proper care of tires conserves rubber, saves gas too! [S.l.]: Schrader in the interest of National Defense, [194-]., 1 print: 2 color (red and blue); 34 x 52 cm. (Box 19)
    At lower right: "1085 Litho'd in USA." Uncle Sam: "I need all the rubber you can save."
  - Enlist in a proud profession! Join the U.S. Cadet Nurse Corps / A lifetime education - free! If you can qualify. [Washington, D.C.]: U.S. Public Health Service Federal Security Agency, [194-]., 1 print: color; 71 x 51 cm. (Box 19)
    Signed in bottom of image: "Edmundson." At bottom: "For information go to you local hospital or write U.S. Cadet Nurse Corps, Box 88, New York, N.Y."
  - Fishing in Holland. [Netherlands?: s.n., 1945?]., 1 print: color; 75 x 51 cm. (Box 19)
    Dutch poster printed for display in Allied English-speaking countries. Poster also printed in Spanish. (Publication information from Midden-Holland Regional Archives).
  - Give it your best! Washington, D.C.: Office of War Information, 1942 (Washington, D.C.: U.S. Government Printing Office)., 1 print: color; 51 x 72 cm. (Box 19)
    Unsigned (Artist information from Bird and Rubenstein). At lower right: "Poster No. 9 / 1942--O-488228."
  - He's going for you! Buy War Bonds. [S.l.]: Abbot, [194-]., 1 print: color; 32 x 25 cm. (Box 19)
    A tear out from the Abbott prescription supply company client newsletter "What's New." Verso text explains Abbott's advertising and sales services.
  - Hot air in Holland. [Netherlands?: s.n., 1945?]., 1 print: color; 75 x 51 cm. (Box 19)
  - I'm counting on you! Don't discuss: troop movements ship sailings war equipment. Washington, D.C.: Office of War Information, 1943 ([Washington, D.C.]: U.S. Government Printing Office)., 1 print: color; 71 x 51 cm. (Box 19)
    Signed in lower left of image: "L Helguera." At bottom: "OWI Poster No.78 / 1943--O-534057."
  - Ours...to fight for / Freedom from fear. Washington, D.C.: Office of War Information, 1943 (Washington, D.C.: U.S. Government Printing Office)., 1 print: color; 71 x 51 cm. (Box 19)